Punk Music Library PUNK007
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 2: 7"
  - Aquarium, The - Performer (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bad Brains - Pay To Cum (Label: Roir ), Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Coke Bust - Degradation (Label: Grave Mistake), Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Coke Bust/Vaccine - Split (Label: Refuse Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Coup Savage And The Snips - Sneak (Label: Paroxysm), Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Edie Sedgwick - Love Gets Lovelier Every Day (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Egghunt - Me and You (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Fidelity Jones - Venus (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Fordists - Economic Stimulus (Label: Fordist Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fordists - Gerald Ford (Label: Fordist Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fugazi - Furniture (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Gamma Rays - Dynamite (Label: Teenbeat), Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Gamma Rays - Lovely (Label: Teenbeat), Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Georgie James - Cake Parade (Label: Saddle Creek), Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Jawbox - Tongues (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Killer Bees, The - Buzz'n The Town (Label: Windian Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Las Mordidas - Surrounded (Label: Dischord Half Label), Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Las Palabras - Mariposas b/w Un Momento (Label: Fox Hollow Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Machetres - s/t (Label: Dischord Half Label), Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Mary Christ - S/t (Label: Hesitation Wound), Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - MFD - All Of This (Label: DSI Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - MFD - Chapter 3 (Label: DSI Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Minor Threat - First Demo Tape (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Minor Threat - Salad Days (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Monument - s/t (Label: Monument Recordings), Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Office Of Future Plans - Harden Your Heart (Label: Artic Rodeo), Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Pizza / Tideland - Split (Label: Cosmic Debris), Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Priests - Radiation (Label: Sister Polygon ), Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Puff Pieces - 4 Song 7" (Label: Lovitt Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Rites Of Spring - All Through A Life (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Severin - 2 song (Label: Dischord Half Label), Undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Shirks - Action Men (Label: Cricket Cemetery), Undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Shirks - Dangerous (Label: Big Neck Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Shirks, The - Disease (Label: Windian Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - SOA - First Demo 12/29/80 (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Stigmatics - s/t (Label: Dischord Half Label), Undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - STOP WORRYING AND (Love the Bomb) - Haunting (Label: Big Neck Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Teen Idles - 6 Song (Label: Dischord), Undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Title Tracks - Every Little Bit Hurts / Found Out (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Black Market Baby, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Girls Against Boys - Park Avenue, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Give - I am Live, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Initial Reaction -, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Make Up - U R My, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Max Levine Ensemble - Elephant in the Room, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Pietasters - Soul Sammich, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Pietasters - The Ska-Rumptious, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Polar/Mass Movement of the Moth - split, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Protester - s/t, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Satan's Satyrs - Black Souls, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Satan's Satyrs - Live at the Black Cat, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Shitfit/Moment of Youth - split ep, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Sweetbelly Freakdown -, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Troll Tax, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Troops of Tomorrow, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - United 121/Mutiny - split, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Aftermath, The - Goodbye to Washington, Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Chain And The Gang - Mum's the Word (Label: Radical Elite Records), 2014 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Coke Bust - Degredation (Label: Grave Mistake Records), 2011 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    46
  - Crispus Attucks - Yo Peho, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - De-sensitized - The Hidden Hand, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Give - Boots of Faith (Label: Deranged Records), 2010 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    176
  - Government Issue - First Demo, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Government Issue - Make An Effort (Label: Doctor Strange Records), 2002 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    5
  - Holy rollers - Origami Sessions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Images - Dreams are Real, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Malefice - Overbord (Label: DSI Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Obsessed, The - Iron and Stone, Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Office of Future Plans - Daria (Label: Lovitt Records), 2013 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    74
  - Reptile House - I Stumble as the Crow Flies, Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Set to Explode - Feel the Rage, Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Shirks - DC is Doomed (Label: Self Released), Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Shirks - The Cry Cry Cry (Label: Grave Mistake), 2011 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    45
  - Shirks, The - Disease, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Shoutbus - s/t, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Slickee Boys - When I Go to the Beach, Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Slickee Boys - Hot and Cool (Label: Dacoit), Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Spitfires United/Alleged Bricks - Piss and Vinegar ep, Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Striking Distance - The Fuse is Lit, Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Suspects, The - s/t, Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - 86 Mentality - On the Loose EP Test Press (Label: Grave Mistake Records), 2005 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - 86 Mentality - Final Exit Test Press, Undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Crispus Attucks - Da Nada, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Crispus Attucks - s/t, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Series 3: Cassettes
  - Young Caucasians - Shroud of Elvis, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Velvet Monkeys - Everything is Right, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beginners Mynd - Beginners Mynd (Label: Burger), Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - (last) seconds (of) - a GO-GO (Label: honey touch/baby cutter), Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - (last) seconds (of) - Welcome to the Mothership, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Red Out - "integument and suckers", Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hundred Dollar bill - Buy Back Your Children, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Savage Boys and Girls Club - (Keepin it Real) for the Kids, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Tilden Shirtwaist Fire - Intent on the Sounds, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Jawbox - Now Hear This II, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Challenger Commission - Briefcase Song, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Elusive - The Elusive, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Various - In It Together Mixtape, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Blockhead - Guts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Government Issue - Joyride, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Immoral Discipline - Boots and Braces, Stars and Stripes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hated - Awl (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Fire Party - 12/87, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Various - Embassy Tapes 1990 to 1992, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ape House - Rat Trap, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Priests - Tape Two, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cassettes - Neath the Pale Moon, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Cassettes - Countach, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Dudes - Greatest Hits, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Teen Liver, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Jail Solidarity - Any Space, Whatever, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Aloners - Demo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Carni Klirs - Drift and Fade, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Mind/Glow - Demo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Nuclear Age - Demo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Public Suicide - Demo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Red Death - Demo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Zoom - Demo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Series 4: CDs
  - Various - Begin Live Transmission/Radio CPR, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Half Beat - Half Mess, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mess Up the Mess - You Remind Me of Summer Vacation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Beat Police - Our Own Farm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - NRIs - Playground/The Charm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Title Tracks - In Blank, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Title Tracks - It Was Easy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Routineers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Twenty Years of Dischord, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mobius Strip - A Knee in the Back, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pash - Kingwood (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Del Cielo - Us Vs Them (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Various - Don't Know When I'll be Back Again (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Various - Keep Singing (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mass Movement of the Moth - Outerspace (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Gina Young - She's So Androgynous (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Kathy Cashel - The Question is Yes (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Pash - The Best Gun (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Trophy Wife - Patience Fury (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Various - With Literacy and Justice for All (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1905 - Voice (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Songs of August - 1902 (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Variouos - And Tonight the City Safely Sleeps (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Various - This is a Care Package (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Measles Mumps Rubella - Fantastic Success, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 7 Door Sedan - Killer Good (Label: Two Sixty AC), Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alice Despard Group - Thinning of the Veil (Label: Arlingtone Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - All Scars - Lunar Magus (Label: Dischord Half Label), Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Antelope - Reflector (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    DIS157CD
  - Apes - Ghost Games (Label: Gypsy Eyes), Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Autoclave - s/t (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Beauty Pill - Cigarette Girl From The Future (Label: Dischord Half Label), Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Black Market Baby - Coulda (Label: Doctor Strange Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chumps - Problem with Sax (Label: Afterburn Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Circus Lupus - Super Genius (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Coke Bust - Confined (Label: Grave Mistake), Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Cranium, The - New Music For A New Kitchen (Label: Slowdime), Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Dag Nasty - Can I Say? and 6 (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Del Cielo - Us Vs Them (Label: Lovitt Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Don Zientara - 16 Songs (Label: Northern Liberties), Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Edsel - Extended Play (Label: Dischord Half Label), Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Faith Void - Faith/Void/Faith (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Fire Party - 19 songs (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Frodus - Radioactivity (Label: Magic Bullet Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fugazi - 13 Songs (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Happy Go Licky - Will Play (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Hoover - Lurid Traversal of Rte. 7 (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Ignition - Complete Services (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Lungfish - Feral Hymns (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Lungfish - Love is Love (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Lungfish - Necrophones (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Lungfish - Sound In Time (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Mary Timony - Ex Hex (Label: Lookout Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mass Movement Of The Moth - Outerspace (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mass Movement Of The Moth / Catalyst - Split (Label: Perpetual Motion Machine), Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Measles Mumps Rubella - Fantastic Success (Label: Doubling Cube Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Measles Mumps Rubella - Fountain Of Youth b/w Fear No Water (Label: Troubleman Unlimited), Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan - Side Effects (Label: Crank Automotive), Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Minor Threat - Complete Discography (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Nation of Ulysses - Embassy Tapes (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Norman Mayer Group - In Memory (Label: Dischord Half Label), Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Q and Not U - Power (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Scream - Still Screaming / This Side Up (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Shudder To Think - Curses Spells Voodoo… (Label: Sammich Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Shudder To Think - Get Your Goat (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Shudder To Think - Funeral At The Movies / Ten Spot (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Signs Point to Yes - Are We There Yet? (Label: Suffragette Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Skewbald/Grand Union - Skewbald/Grand Union (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Slant 6 - Soda Pop*Rip Off (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Soul Side - Soon Come Happy (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Soulside - Less Deep Inside, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Statehood - Lies and Rhetoric (Label: Self Released), Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Trusty - Goodbye, Dr. Fate (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Tsunami - A Brilliant Mistake (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Tsunami - Deep End (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Tsunami - Heart's Tremolo (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Various Artists - 20 Years of Dischord (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Various Artists - 30 Seconds over DC (Label: 2.13.61), Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Various Artists - And Tonight The City Safely Sleeps (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Various Artists - Dischord 1981: The Year In Seven Inches (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Various Artists - Don't Know When I'll Be Back Again (Veteran compilation) (Label: Exotic Fever), Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Various Artists - Radio CPR: Begin Live Transmission (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Various Artists - State Of The Union (Label: Dischord Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Various Artists - Teen Smash Hits (Label: Level Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Various Artists - Working Holiday Compilation (Label: Simple Machines), Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Vile Cherubs - The Man Who Has (Label: Afterburn Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Weird War - If You Can't Beat... (Label: Drag City Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Weird War - Illuminated By Night (Label: Drag City Records), Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)